{"sents": {"0": [{"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "1", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "The man the dinner burned."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "2", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Many house were destroyed by the flood."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "3", "gram": "PP*", "answer": "", "sent": "The boy is speak to a policeman."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did Janie sleep with her parents last night?", "num": "4", "gram": "PT", "answer": "n", "sent": "Janie slept with her dolls last night."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Does Mary open her window?", "num": "5", "gram": "DET", "answer": "y", "sent": "Mary opens the windows in her room."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "6", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Is waiting Sally in the car?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "Does John have a cat?", "num": "7", "gram": "3PS", "answer": "n", "sent": "John's dog always waits for him outside."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Do the rabbits get carrots?", "num": "8", "gram": "WO", "answer": "y", "sent": "The boy feeds the rabbits carrots."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "9", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Is being Lucy held by his mother?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did a crow flew into the attic?", "num": "10", "gram": "PT", "answer": "n", "sent": "A bat flew into our attic yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did the boys play on swings?", "num": "11", "gram": "PL", "answer": "y", "sent": "Three boys played on the swings."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did John sing in the opera?", "num": "12", "gram": "PT", "answer": "n", "sent": "John sang for the church choir yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "13", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Drinks the young man."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "14", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "We are teaching herself the Spanish alphabet."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "15", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "I want you will go to school."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Will Roy leave early?", "num": "16", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "y", "sent": "Roy will be leaving the party early."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did the boy put a glass in the kitchen?", "num": "17", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "n", "sent": "The boy put the book in the kitchen"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "18", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "Right this minute the ship is sinking."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "19", "gram": "PP*", "answer": "", "sent": "Janet is wear the dress right now."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Do the girls enjoy singing?", "num": "20", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "y", "sent": "The girls enjoy singing Karaoke."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "21", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "Tom walked the hall down to Stephanie."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "22", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the woman satted on her porch."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "23", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Alex brought corns to the company picnic."}, {"group": "A", "question": "The man was in his closet?", "num": "24", "gram": "PM", "answer": "n", "sent": "She stepped in the room carefully."}, {"group": "A", "question": "The men went to the club?", "num": "25", "gram": "PL", "answer": "y", "sent": "Many men came to the club."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "26", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Grace cooks eggs for Jerry last night."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "27", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Can the boy can drive a tractor?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did the fireman talk with the man?", "num": "28", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "n", "sent": "The policeman was talking to a woman."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Was there a book in the sentence?", "num": "29", "gram": "WHSUB", "answer": "y", "sent": "Where did she put the book?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "Does Ryan live with Danny?", "num": "30", "gram": "IC", "answer": "n", "sent": "Ryan lives with Max every summer."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "31", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Danced Bill at the party yesterday?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did the children go to the theater?", "num": "32", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "y", "sent": "They took their children to the theater."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Was John thinking about airplanes?", "num": "33", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "n", "sent": "John should have given food to Cindy."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "34", "gram": "TENSE*", "answer": "", "sent": "Where did Arnie hunted last year?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "35", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "What the boy will read next?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "Was a tire in the sentence?", "num": "36", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "y", "sent": "He is fixing the bicycle tire."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "37", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Fred will be get a raise tomorrow."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Did the elephant jump?", "num": "38", "gram": "PM", "answer": "n", "sent": "The horse jumped over the fence yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "Was the season summer?", "num": "39", "gram": "WH", "answer": "y", "sent": "Where do you work during the summer?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "40", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Leonard should has written to Katrina."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "41", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "Tammy bought rice at the grocery store."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "42", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "Who you meet every day?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "43", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Two mouses ran into the house."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "44", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "Susan is making some cookies for us."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "45", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "The cat is hiding underneath the couch."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "46", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Arnold may have be sleeping."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "47", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "I hope you will go to Canada."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "48", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Tom drove himselve's sister to the concert."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "49", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Does Jane learn math from Mr. Thompson?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "50", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the hunter shot a deer."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "51", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "At this moment Judy shops."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "52", "gram": "WHSUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "Why did the company send?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "53", "gram": "PM", "answer": "", "sent": "The glass broke into pieces."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "54", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Has the king been served his dinner?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "55", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "We ate the whole pizza by ourselves."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "56", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Will Larry feed the cat tomorrow?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "57", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Linda a cake baked John."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "58", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the books falled off the shelves."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "59", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Can the little girl ride a bicycle?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "60", "gram": "DET*", "answer": "", "sent": "Larry went the home after the party."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "61", "gram": "DET", "answer": "", "sent": "Tom is reading a book upstairs."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "62", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "What is Martha bringing to the party?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "63", "gram": "3PS*", "answer": "", "sent": "Terri frequently Talk with Martha."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "64", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "What does Janet pay her gardener?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "65", "gram": "WO", "answer": "", "sent": "The tall woman paints."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "66", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the man make a chocolate cake."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "67", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The little boys laughed the clown."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "68", "gram": "WO", "answer": "", "sent": "The girl likes the movie."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "69", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Paul often is meeting George at school."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "70", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Will wear Harry his tie to work?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "71", "gram": "TPS", "answer": "", "sent": "Every Friday our neighbor washes her car."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "72", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "The kids would have eaten by now."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "73", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Bites the scary dog."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "74", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Can George hear us from there?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "75", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "When will Sam fix his car?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "76", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the baby throwed a cat."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "77", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Right now Bart watched a game."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "78", "gram": "WHSUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "Who did the teacher smile?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "79", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "Right now Kate is dreaming about Greg."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "80", "gram": "DET*", "answer": "", "sent": "Mrs. Johnson went to library yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "81", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "The ball the boy caught."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "82", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "The farmers were hoping for rain."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "83", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "Does Martha use her microwave oven?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "84", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Sandy filled the jar with cookies yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "85", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "Todd has many coats in his closet."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "86", "gram": "PET*", "answer": "", "sent": "A boys are going to the zoo."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "87", "gram": "DET", "answer": "", "sent": "Andrew is helping Judy build a house."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "88", "gram": "PM", "answer": "", "sent": "The man climbed up the ladder carefully."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "89", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "George says his prayers much too softly."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "90", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "A shoe salesman always sees many foots."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "91", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "What do they sell at the store?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "92", "gram": "PP", "answer": "", "sent": "The dog is barking at the mailman."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "93", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "A snake bit she one the leg."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "94", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Will Harry be blamed for the accident?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "95", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "They stood the line in very patiently."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "96", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Santa hid his money yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "97", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Sheeps graze in the field."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "98", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday Sam is standing in the rain."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "99", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Did Janet swim in the race yesterday?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "100", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Carol is cooking dinner for hers family."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "101", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The man allows his son watch TV."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "102", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "The bird has fall from the tree."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "103", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "You must have skipped lunch"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "104", "gram": "TPS*", "answer": "", "sent": "Mrs. Sampson clean her house every Wednesday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "105", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "Kevin called Amy for a date up."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "106", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "Anna lost two teeth in the fight."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "107", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Christina cut himself."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "108", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the teacher sented a letter."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "109", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Knows John the answers?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "110", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Jeff has been lie to his father."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "111", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "Where Ted is working this summer?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "112", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "A tourist a question asked grandpa."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "113", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Should have Timothy gone to the party?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "114", "gram": "WHSUB", "answer": "", "sent": "Why did the man go?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "115", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "George has been cleaning for hours."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "116", "gram": "DET*", "answer": "", "sent": "Girl played with her friend outside."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "117", "gram": "PP", "answer": "", "sent": "The woman is holding her newborn baby."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "118", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "The man lets his son watch TV."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "119", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Have you seen Jane's new baby?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "120", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Them worked on the project all night."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "121", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "Ken counted all his pennies last night."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "122", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "The farmer bought two pig."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "123", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "When they leave for Mexico?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "124", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "The girl's swimsuit is full of sand."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "125", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "Did Bobby stayed at home last night."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "126", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "Linda poured herself a glass of lemonade."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "127", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The girls want watching TV."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "128", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Will the girl can hurt the kitten?"}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "129", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday Mrs. Smith die in her sleep."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "130", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Chris may is moving to Chicago tomorrow."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "131", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "A policeman gave Tom a ticket yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "132", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "He came my house at six."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "133", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "Tim looked the new cars at yesterday."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "134", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "Jenna raced her friend to the fence."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "135", "gram": "DET", "answer": "", "sent": "The men played basketball at school."}, {"group": "A", "question": "", "num": "136", "gram": "PM", "answer": "", "sent": "The man looked the new cars over yesterday."}], "1": [{"group": "B", "question": "Did the tourist ask the widow?", "num": "1", "gram": "WO", "answer": "n", "sent": "A tourist asked grandpa a question."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Was it the teacher who smiled?", "num": "2", "gram": "WHSUG", "answer": "y", "sent": "When did the teacher smile?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did Linda bake cookies?", "num": "3", "gram": "WO", "answer": "n", "sent": "Linda baked John a cake."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "4", "gram": "PP*", "answer": "", "sent": "The woman is hold her newborn baby."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "5", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "Carol is cooking dinner for her family."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "6", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "Where you work during the summer?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "7", "gram": "SUG*", "answer": "", "sent": "The man lets his son to watch TV."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Is Janet wearing a dress?", "num": "8", "gram": "PP", "answer": "y", "sent": "Janet is wearing the dress right now."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "9", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "The cat is hide underneath the couch."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Does the cat bite?", "num": "10", "gram": "WO", "answer": "n", "sent": "The scary dog bites."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "11", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "When Sam will fix his car?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "12", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Roy will is leaving the party early."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "13", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Will Larry will feed the cat tomorrow?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "Where houses destroyed?", "num": "14", "gram": "PL", "answer": "y", "sent": "Many houses were destroyed by the flood."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "15", "gram": "DEL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Mary opens a windows in her room."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "16", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Santa hidded his money yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "17", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Learns Jane math from Mr. Thompson."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did a cow bite her?", "num": "18", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "n", "sent": "A snake bit her on the leg."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did the sentence mention school?", "num": "19", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "y", "sent": "I want you to go to school."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did the farmer buy two horses?", "num": "20", "gram": "PL", "answer": "n", "sent": "The farmer bought two pigs."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did Mrs. Johnson go to the library?", "num": "21", "gram": "DET", "answer": "y", "sent": "Mrs. Johnson went to the library yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "22", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "John should have give food to Cindy."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "23", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Right this minute the ship sinks."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did Bobby stand in the rain?", "num": "24", "gram": "IC", "answer": "n", "sent": "Yesterday Sam stood in the rain."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "25", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "What does Janet pays her gardener?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "26", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Sandy fill the jar with cookies yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Were they patient in line?", "num": "27", "gram": "PM", "answer": "y", "sent": "They stood in the line very patiently."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did the boy pass a test?", "num": "28", "gram": "WO", "answer": "n", "sent": "The boy caught the ball."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Was there a company in the sentence?", "num": "29", "gram": "WHSUB", "answer": "y", "sent": "What did the company send?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "30", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Anna lost two teeths in the fight."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did the girls want to go to the mall?", "num": "31", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "n", "sent": "The girls want to watch TV."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "32", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "Janie sleeped with her dolls last night."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "33", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "The man climbed the ladder up carefully."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "34", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Will be Harry blamed for the accident?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did someone cut themself?", "num": "35", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "y", "sent": "Christina cut herself."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Was there a school in the sentence?", "num": "36", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "n", "sent": "Is Sally waiting in the car?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "37", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "The girl's swimsuit is full of sands."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "38", "gram": "3PS*", "answer": "", "sent": "Every Friday our neighbor wash her car."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "39", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the hunter shoots a deer."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Dose Paul meet George?", "num": "40", "gram": "IC", "answer": "y", "sent": "Paul often meets George at school."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "41", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "The horse jumped the fence over yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did the man burn his house?", "num": "42", "gram": "WO", "answer": "n", "sent": "The man burned the dinner."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "43", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The girls enjoy to sing Karaoke."}, {"group": "B", "question": "Did they work on the project?", "num": "44", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "y", "sent": "They worked on the project all night."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "45", "gram": "DET", "answer": "", "sent": "Larry went home after the party."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "46", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "George says much too softly."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "47", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Arnold may have been sleeping."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "48", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Right now Kate drempt about Greg."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "49", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday Mrs. Smith died in her sleep."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "50", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Is Lucy being held by his mother?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "51", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Jenna raced herselves friend to the fence."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "52", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Todd has many coat in his closet."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "53", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "Two mice ran into the house."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "54", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "Alex brought corn to the company picnic."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "55", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "A bat flewed into our attic yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "56", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the man made a chocolate cake."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "57", "gram": "WO", "answer": "", "sent": "The young man drinks."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "58", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "Who do you meet every day?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "59", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "The kids would has eaten by now."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "60", "gram": "WHSUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "What did the man go?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "61", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The farmers were hoping rain."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "62", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "Right now Bart is watching a game."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "63", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the baby threw a cat."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "64", "gram": "PM", "answer": "", "sent": "Tom waked down the hall to Stephanie."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "65", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "You must have skip lunch"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "66", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Does John know the answers?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "67", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Linda poured themselves a glass of lemonade."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "68", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "What will the boy read next?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "69", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Have seen you Jane's new baby?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "70", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Can the boy drive a tractor?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "71", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "He came to my house at six."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "72", "gram": "3PS*", "answer": "", "sent": "John's dog always wait for him outside."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "73", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Ryan is living with Max every summer."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "74", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "Where did Arnie hunt last year?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "75", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "Does Martha uses her microwave oven?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "76", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the teacher sent a letter."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "77", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Can George will hear us from there?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "78", "gram": "WHSUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "Why did she put the book?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "79", "gram": "DET*", "answer": "", "sent": "Andrew is helping Judy build house."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "80", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Three boy played on the swings."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "81", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Did Bill dance at the party yesterday?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "82", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "When do they leave for Mexico?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "83", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Fred will be getting a raise tomorrow."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "84", "gram": "PM", "answer": "", "sent": "Kevin called Amy up for a date."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "85", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "What they sell at the store?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "86", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Susan is making some cookies for we."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "87", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Will Harry wear his tie to work?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "88", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the woman sat on her porch."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "89", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "She stepped the room in carefully."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "90", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "A policemen gived Tom a ticket yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "91", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Paints the tall woman."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "92", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Has been the king served his dinner?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "93", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "Tom drove his sister to the concert."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "94", "gram": "PP", "answer": "", "sent": "The boy is speaking to a policeman."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "95", "gram": "PRO", "answer": "", "sent": "We are teaching ourselves the Spanish alphabet."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "96", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "I hope you to go to Canada."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "97", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Chris may be moving to Chicago tomorrow."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "98", "gram": "DET*", "answer": "", "sent": "The men played the basketball at school."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "99", "gram": "DET", "answer": "", "sent": "The girl played with her friend outside."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "100", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "A shoe salesman always sees many feet."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "101", "gram": "WH*", "answer": "", "sent": "What Martha is bringing to the party?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "102", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Tammy bought rices at the grocery store."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "103", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "The little boys laughed at the clown."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "104", "gram": "3PS", "answer": "", "sent": "Mrs. Sampson cleans her house every Wednesday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "105", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "George has be cleaning for hours."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "106", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "Grace cooked eggs for Jerry last night."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "107", "gram": "PM", "answer": "", "sent": "Tim looked at the new cars yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "108", "gram": "PT", "answer": "", "sent": "Yesterday the books fell off the shelves."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "109", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Should Timothy have gone to the party?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "110", "gram": "SUB", "answer": "", "sent": "The man allows his son to watch TV."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "111", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Swam Janet in the race yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "112", "gram": "PP*", "answer": "", "sent": "The dog is bark at the mailman."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "113", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Leonard should have written to Katrina."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "114", "gram": "PL*", "answer": "", "sent": "Many mens came to the club."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "115", "gram": "AUX*", "answer": "", "sent": "Can ride the little girl a bicycle."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "116", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Will the girl hurt the kitten?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "117", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The policeman was talking a woman."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "118", "gram": "3PS", "answer": "", "sent": "Terri frequently talks with Martha."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "119", "gram": "IC*", "answer": "", "sent": "Ken is counting all his pennies last night."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "120", "gram": "IC", "answer": "", "sent": "At this moment Judy is shopping."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "121", "gram": "PT*", "answer": "", "sent": "John sing for the church choir yesterday."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "122", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "The glass broke pieces into."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "123", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "Did Bobby stay at home last night?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "124", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "The bird has fallen from the tree."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "125", "gram": "PL", "answer": "", "sent": "Sheep graze in the field."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "126", "gram": "DET*", "answer": "", "sent": "Tom is reading book upstairs."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "127", "gram": "SUB*", "answer": "", "sent": "The boy put the book at the kitchen."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "128", "gram": "WH", "answer": "", "sent": "Where is Ted working this summer?"}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "129", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "Him is fixing the bicycle tire."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "130", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "They took theirs children to the theater."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "131", "gram": "PM*", "answer": "", "sent": "The man looked the new cars yesterday over."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "132", "gram": "DET", "answer": "", "sent": "The boys are going to the zoo."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "133", "gram": "PRO*", "answer": "", "sent": "We ate the whole pizza by themselves."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "134", "gram": "AUX", "answer": "", "sent": "Jeff has been lying to his father."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "135", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "The boy the rabbits feeds carrots."}, {"group": "B", "question": "", "num": "136", "gram": "WO*", "answer": "", "sent": "The girl the movie likes."}]}}
